[Music]
yes
that's me that's just it was a very
different time wow that's the coolest
picture anybody in our family's ever
taken
yeah on julia you look so hot and i love
that outfit
she broke all my friends hearts mine too
i used to steal
all of her clothes i mean how are you
always so on trend
she insisted you get your perfect skin
from grandma too
yes well good genes so what the hell
happened to me then huh
you know that one nobody's like i always
say eat well sleep well
take care of your skin what
oh sorry i'm reading an article about
how to ask out your subway sandwich
artist
oh i like that for you
uh what's the story with this one yeah
we were in the room oh oh
okay i was in london i just graduated
college
and i was just wandering around i found
myself in the chelsea flower market come
on
it says you're not supposed to order
chips
jesus esther you always get chips
yeah that's my daughter
so back to the photo i was
in the flower market minding my own
business looking at these beautiful
flowers and i get a tap on my shoulder
gentleman says may i take your picture
turns out he is the famous photographer
richard
my mom is so pretty
elegant and fine
her hair looks perfect like a hundred
percent of the time
her features are small and delicate
she's
hotter than your mom i bet but it only
makes me
sad because i look more like my dad
[Music]
i've got my dad's eyebrows i've got my
dad's nose
i've got my dad's shoulders i've got
hair on my toes
gross just the big ones my mom's
graceful as a swan
i look like a hobbit with overalls on
it's bad
i take after my dad she's her father's
daughter daughter
she's her father's daughter daughter
she's her father's girl don't you with
my mouth open
whenever i'm eating my sideburns are out
of control
and your hairline's receding yeah i know
her mom's skin is smooth as
glass but i've got my dad's pores and
his weird flat assets grim
i look more like him she's her father's
daughter daughter
she's her father's daughter daughter
she's her father's girl
big forehead
[Music]
fat calves bad posture
athlete's foot it's not as if you're
unattractive to men
you're just a little bit uglier than you
should have been
thanks grandma that helps it does
[Music]
i go out in pajamas my mom irons her
clothes your dad's got beautiful legs
but i didn't get those what the
it's sad but it's the truth i look like
the daughter with no lines from fiddler
on the roof
and my dad's to blame cause we look the
same
we're exactly like one another i
look like my dad's little brother but
i'm bad at math and have mood swings
like my mom
did you like my song god you need a lot
of attention don't you
you